Heezen-Tharp collection: Pacific Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
- Series I: Pacific Ocean
  - Group 01 - Pacific Ocean Tracks, 17688140
    - 0539 New Zealand Bathymetry Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648838)
      a. Paper. b. From 42˚ to 48˚ South and 169˚ East to 179˚ West. Prepared by the NZ Oceanographic Institute. Plotted on sheet Bounty. 1970.
    - 0540 New Zealand Bathymetry Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648838)
      a. Paper. b. From 65˚ to 68˚ South and 157˚ to 169˚ East. Prepared by the NZ Oceanographic Institute. Plotted on sheet Balleny. 1970.
    - 0541 New Zealand Bathymetry Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648838)
      a. Paper. b. From 48˚ to 65˚ South and 157˚ to 169˚ East. Prepared by the NZ Oceanographic Institute. Plotted on sheet Auckland. 1967.
    - 0542 Tracks in the Eastern one-third of the Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648838)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 0˚ to 67˚ South and 70˚ to 110˚ West. Includes provinces, tracks without depths, and unidentified cruises.
    - 0543 Navigation Tracks / Times for Vema 28 and Robert Connrad 14 (Folder Barcode: 00275648826)
    - 0544 Navigation Tracks / Times for Vema 28 and Robert Connrad 14 (Folder Barcode: 00275648826)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 5˚ to 60˚ North and 95˚ to 165˚ West.
    - 0545 Tracks with Magnetic Profiles (Folder Barcode: 00275648826)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 15˚ North to 50˚ South and 150˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0546 Tracks Between Australia and Japan with Camera Station Numbers (Folder Barcode: 00275648826)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 120˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0547 Tracks over the Darwin Goyut (Folder Barcode: 00275648826)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 21˚ 50’ to 22˚ 30’ North and 171˚ to 172˚ East. Seamount #3. 19 –20 May 1971.
    - 0548 Australian Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648814)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 15˚ to 60˚ South and 105˚ to 165˚ East.
    - 0549 Master Track Chart for the SW Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648814)
      a. Ozalid Paper. b. From 30˚ to 75˚ South and 120˚ East to 60˚ West.
    - 0550 Master Track Chart for the SE Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648814)
      a. Negative Transparency. b. From 35˚ North to 65˚ South and 70˚ to 110˚ West. Includes contours in meters.
    - 0551 Scripps Track Index Sheet (Folder Barcode: 00275648814)
      a. Paper. b. From 18˚ North to 50˚ South and 70˚ to 125˚ West. Covers the central Eastern Pacific. Included US Navy Index blocks.
    - 0552 Scripps Track Index Sheet (Folder Barcode: 00275648814)
      a. Paper. b. From 10˚ North to 50˚ South and 125˚ to 180˚ West. Covers the central Pacific. Included US Navy Index blocks.
    - 0553 Scripps Track Index Sheet (Folder Barcode: 00275648814)
      a. Paper. b. From 20˚ North to 50˚ South and 125˚ to 180˚ East. Covers the central Pacific. Included US Navy Index blocks.
    - 0554 Tracks for the Entire Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648814)
      a. Ozalid Paper. b. Polar projection. Tracks from US Navy and other expeditions.
    - 0555 Tracks for the Aries Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
      a. Tracing Paper. b. From 9˚ to 22˚ North and 156˚ to 173˚ West. Computer plotted, 6-9 May 1971.
    - 0556 Tracks for the Aries Leg 5, Seamount Survey 6 (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
      a. Tracing Paper. b. From 29˚ 10’ to 29˚ 50’ North and 153˚ to 153˚ 50’ East. Computer plotted, 31 May 1971.
    - 0557 Tracks for the Aries Leg 5, DSPD Survey 2 (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 17˚ 20’ to 18˚ North and 175˚ to 175˚ 50’ West. Computer plotted, 10- 11 May 1971.
    - 0558 Tracks for the Aries Leg 5, DSPD Survey 3 (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
    - 0559 North Pacific Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 60˚ North and 105˚ West to 165˚ East.
    - 0560 Master Track Chart (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ to 60˚ North and 95˚ West to 165˚ East. Color –coded tracks and Matthew’s numbers.
    - 0561 Index to Lamont Profiler Records (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ to 165˚ East. Covers the NW Pacific, Map 5.
    - 0562 Index to Lamont Profiler Records (Folder Barcode: 00275648802)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ to 165˚ East. Color-coded tracks. Covers the NW Pacific, Map 5.
    - 0563 Index to Lamont Profiler Records (Folder Barcode: 00275648796)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 30˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ West to 165˚ East. Cover the Northern Pacific, Map 6N.
    - 0564 Index to Lamont Profiler Records (Folder Barcode: 00275648796)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 30˚ to 60˚ North and 110˚ West to 165˚ East. Cover the Northern Pacific, Map 6N. (Data different from 0563).
    - 0565 Index to Lamont Profiler Records (Folder Barcode: 00275648796)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 30˚ North and 95˚ to 170˚ West. Map 6A. From December 1960 to January 1971.
    - 0566 Index to Lamont Profiler Records (Folder Barcode: 00275648796)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 15˚ to 60˚ South and 95˚ West to 165˚ East. Map 10, covers the central Pacific.
    - 0567 Tracks for Dredged Station #28 (Folder Barcode: 00275648796)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ 20’ to 31˚ North and 158˚ to 158˚ 55’ East. From 29-30 May 1971.
    - 0568 Tracks for Dredged Station #28 (Folder Barcode: 00275648796)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ 20’ to 31˚ North and 158˚ to 158˚ 55’ East. From the ship – Thomas Washington.
    - 0569 Tracks for Dredged Station #28 (Folder Barcode: 00275648796)
      a. Tracing paper. b. From 30˚ to 31˚ North and 158˚ to 158˚ 55’ East. Aries V, 29-30 May 1971.
    - 0570 Tracks for Vema 24-07 (Folder Barcode: 00275648784)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 0˚ to 6˚ North and 143˚ to 154˚ East. Manila to Townsville. July 3 1967.
    - 0571 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648784)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 24˚ North and 157˚ to 167˚ West. Sheet 1 and 1 a.
    - 0572 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648784)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 24˚ North and 168˚ to 178˚ West. Sheet 2.
    - 0573 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648784)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 18˚ North and 174˚ to 178˚ West. Sheet 2a.
    - 0574 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648784)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 24˚ North and 177˚ West to 178˚ East. Sheet 3.
    - 0575 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648784)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 24˚ North and 176˚ to 177˚ East. Sheet 4.
    - 0576 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648784)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 24˚ North and 165˚ to 173˚ East. Sheet 5.
    - 0577 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648772)
      a. Paper. b. From 17˚ to 24˚ North and 158˚ to 167˚ East. Sheet 6.
    - 0578 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648772)
      a. Paper. b. From 23˚ to 30˚ North and 154˚ to 168˚ East. Sheet 7.
    - 0579 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648772)
      a. Paper. b. From 29˚ to 36˚ North and 151˚ to 160˚ East. Sheet 8.
    - 0579 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648772)
    - 0580 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648772)
      a. Paper. b. From 29˚ to 36˚ North and 146˚ to 154˚ East. Sheet 9.
    - 0581 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648772)
      a. Paper. b. From 29˚ to 36˚ North and 142˚ to 148˚ East. Sheet 10.
    - 0582 Aries Navigation Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648772)
      a. Paper. b. From 29˚ to 36˚ North and 138˚ to 143˚ East. Sheet 11.
    - 0583 Konakioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648760)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 8˚ 58’ to 9˚ 42’ North and 158˚ to 159˚ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May, June, August 1971.
    - 0584 Konakioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648760)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 18˚ 37’ North and 159˚ 45’ to 160˚ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May, June, August 1971.
    - 0585 Konakioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648760)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 18˚ 37’ North and 159˚ 40’ to 160˚ 22’ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May, June, August 1971.
    - 0586 Konakioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648760)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 17˚ to 21˚ North and 159˚ to 164˚ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May, June, August 1971.
    - 0587 Konakioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648760)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 13˚ to 18˚ North and 157˚ to 163˚ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May 1971.
    - 0588 Konakioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648760)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 19˚ to 24˚ North and 164˚ to 171˚ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May 1971.
    - 0589 Konakioeki Site Survey (Folder Barcode: 00275648760)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 23˚ to 27˚ North and 170˚ to 178˚ East. Hawaii to Ontag Java Plateau. May 1971.
    - 0590 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 158˚ to 164˚ East. Hawaii to Midway. Number 1 of 10. 27-29 March 1967.
    - 0591 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 163˚ to 173˚ West. Hawaii to Midway. Number 2 of 10. 30 March to 1 April 1967.
    - 0592 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 173˚ to 176˚ West. Hawaii to Midway. Number 3 of 10. 2 April 1967.
    - 0593 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ North and 176˚ to 180˚ West. Hawaii to Midway. Number 4 of 10. 3-4 April 1967.
    - 0594 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ North and 169˚ to 179˚ West. Hawaii to Midway. Number 5 of 10. 6-8 April 1967.
    - 0595 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 159˚ to 170˚ East. Hawaii to Midway. Number 6 of 10. 9-12 April 1967.
    - 0596 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 159˚ to 169˚ East. Hawaii to Midway. Number 7 of 10. 13 April 1967.
    - 0597 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 169˚ to 172˚ East. Hawaii to Midway. Number 8 of 10. 17 April 1967.
    - 0598 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648759)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 24˚ to 30˚ North and 171˚ to 180˚ East. Hawaii to Midway. Number 9 of 10. 18-20 April 1967.
    - 0599 Vema 24 Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 24˚ to 30˚ North and 177˚ to 180˚ West. Hawaii to Midway. Number 10 of 10. 21-22 April 1967.
    - 0600 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 24˚ to 30˚ North and 177˚ to 179˚ West. Midway to Manila. Number 1 of 15. 25-26 April 1967.
    - 0601 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 178˚ to 180˚ West. Midway to Manila. Number 2 of 15. 27-28 April 1967.
    - 0602 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 179˚ to 180˚ West. Midway to Manila. Number 3 of 15. 30 April 1967.
    - 0603 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 178˚ to 180˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 4 of 15. 1 May 1967.
    - 0604 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ North and 172˚ to 180˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 5 of 15. 2-4 May 1967.
    - 0605 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 0˚ to 6˚ North and 66˚ to 173˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 6 of 15. 5-7 May 1967.
    - 0606 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 0˚ to 6˚ North and 155˚ to 166˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 7 of 15. 8-11 May 1967.
    - 0607 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ North and 151˚ to 155˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 8 of 15. 12-13 May 1967.
    - 0608 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 147˚ to 152˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 9 of 15. 14-15 May 1967.
    - 0609 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 147˚ to 148˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 10 of 15.
    - 0610 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 144˚ to 147˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 11 of 15.
    - 0611 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 142˚ to 145˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 12 of 15. 17 May 1967.
    - 0612 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 131˚ to 142˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 13 of 15. 18-20 May 1967.
    - 0613 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 120˚ to 131˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 14 of 15. 21-24 May 1967.
    - 0614 Vema 24, Leg 5 (Folder Barcode: 00275648747)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 118˚ to 121˚ East. Midway to Manila. Number 15 of 15. 25 May 1967.
    - 0615 Title Track Composite Sheet (Folder Barcode: 00275648735)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ South to 30˚ North and 150˚ West to 120˚ East.
    - 0616 Tracks and Matthew’s Areas for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648735)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ South to 30˚ North and 60˚ to 150˚ West. J.L.M. Worksheet
    - 0617 Incomplete Compilations for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648735)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ South to 30˚ North and 60˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0618 Composite Tracks for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648735)
    - 0619 Color-coded Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648735)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 60˚ to 85˚ West.
    - 0620 Color-coded Tracks for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648735)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 5˚ North to 30˚ South and 70˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0621 Color-coded Tracks for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648735)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ North to 30˚ South and 70˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0622 Color-coded Tracks for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 60˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0623 Color-coded Tracks for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
    - 0624 Color-coded Tracks for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 70˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0625 Color-coded Tracks for the East-Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
    - 0626 Color-coded Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ North to 30˚ South and 70˚ to 160˚ West. Cover 1505N.
    - 0627 Color-coded Tracks for the SW Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0628 Color-coded Tracks for the SE Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 20˚ North to 40˚ South and 20˚ East to 85˚ West.
    - 0629 Color-coded Tracks for the SW Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 150˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0630 Color-coded Tracks for the SW Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648723)
    - 0631 Track Chart of Expeditions in the East Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648711)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 5˚ to 60˚ North and 80˚ to 165˚ West. By Scripps for the Bell Telephone laboratories, December 1965.
    - 0632 Track Diagram Eastern Micronesia (Folder Barcode: 00275648711)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 10˚ South to 30˚ North and 160˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0633 Track Diagram Eastern Micronesia (Folder Barcode: 00275648711)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 30˚ North and 160˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0634 Index to Lamont Profiler Records, NW Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648711)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 60˚ North and 65˚ to 165˚ East. Map 5-b.
    - 0635 Index to Lamont Profiler Records, NW Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648711)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 60˚ North and 65˚ to 165˚ East. Map 5.
    - 0636 Scripps Tracks for the North Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648711)
      a. Paper. b. From 20˚ to 60˚ North and 100˚ to 165˚ West.
    - 0637 Index to Lamon Profilers Records Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 60˚ North and 95˚ West to 165˚ East. Map 6.
    - 0638 Index to Lamon Profilers Records Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 60˚ North and 95˚ West to 165˚ East. Map 6a.
    - 0639 Index to Lamon Profilers Records Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ South to 60˚ North and 95˚ West to 165˚ East. Map 6a. Includes color-coded grid.
    - 0640 Index to Lamon Profilers Records Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ to 60˚ North and 95˚ West to 165˚ East. Map 6b.
    - 0641 Index to Lamon Profilers Records Northeast Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 10˚ to 60˚ North and 95˚ West to 165˚ East. Map 6c.
    - 0642 Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 60˚ to 70˚ South and 120˚ to 150˚ West.
    - 0643 Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ to 72˚ South and 100˚ to 120˚ East.
    - 0644 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 20˚ to 30˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0645 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564870A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 20˚ to 30˚ South and 100˚ to 130˚ East.
    - 0646 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648693)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 90˚ to 120˚ East.
    - 0647 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648693)
    - 0648 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648693)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 15˚ to 30˚ South and 160˚ East to 160˚ West.
    - 0649 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648693)
    - 0650 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648693)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 150˚ West to 120˚ East.
    - 0651 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648693)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 120˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0652 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648693)
    - 0653 Color-coded Tracks for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648681)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 72˚ South and 120˚ to 170˚ East.
    - 0654 Composite Sheet – One Track for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648681)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 50˚ South 120˚ East.
    - 0655 Composite Sheet for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648681)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 30˚ to 70˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West.
    - 0656 Composite Sheet for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648681)
    - 0657 Composite Sheet for the Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648681)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ to 70˚ South and 120˚ East to 150˚ West. JLM Worksheet.
    - 0658 Southwest Pacific Tracks (Folder Barcode: 00275648681)
    - 0659 Index to Lamont Profiler Records Southwest Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648681)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 15˚ to 70˚ South and 165˚ East to 100˚ West. Map 10.
    - 0660 Tracks from the Peru- Chile Trench (Folder Barcode: 0027564867A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 20˚ to 45˚ South and 70˚ to 90˚ West.
    - 0661 Track Chart South of Australia (Folder Barcode: 0027564867A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 30˚ to 65˚ South and 120˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0662 Index to Lamont Profiler Records SW Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564867A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 15˚ to 70˚ South and 100˚ West to 165˚ East. Map 10b.
    - 0663 Index to Lamont Profiler Records SE Pacific (Folder Barcode: 0027564867A)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 15˚ to 70˚ South and 100˚ West to 165˚ East.
    - 0664 Pacific Tracks (Folder Barcode: 0027564867A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 18˚ to 35˚ North and 158˚ to 165˚ West. Rolled item.
    - 0665 Pacific Tracks (Folder Barcode: 0027564867A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 18˚ North to 46˚ 40’ South and 67˚ to 90˚ West. Rolled item. Color- coded pen and ink tracks.
    - 0666 Pacific Tracks (Folder Barcode: 0027564867A)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. Rolled item.
    - 0667 Track diagram Eastern Micornesia (Folder Barcode: 00275648668)
      a. Negative transparency. b. From 10˚ South to 30˚ North and 160˚ to 180˚ East.
    - 0668 Profile Index Chart (Folder Barcode: 00275648668)
      a. Positive transparency. b. From 0˚ to 25˚ North and 80˚ to 135˚ West. Prepared by Smith, Chase, Farrell, Taylor, and Weed of the Scripps Institution for the Bell Telephone Laboratories. Chart 3B South, Dec. 1965.
    - 0669 Scripps Track Index of the Central Pacific (Folder Barcode: 00275648668)
      a. Frosted acetate. b. From 18˚ North to 25˚ South and 125˚ to 180˚ West. Summary sheet, no. 2 of 2.
    - 0670 Eastern Pacific and Gulf of Mexico Track and Contour sheet (Folder Barcode: 00275648656)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 35˚ North to 67˚ South and 70˚ to 110˚ West. 18 August 1974.
    - 0671 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648656)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ North to 24˚ South and 158˚ to 163˚ West. Sheet no. 1 of 9. 2-3 October, 1968.
    - 0672 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648656)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 161˚ to 168˚ West. Sheet no. 2 of 9. 4-6 October 1968.
    - 0673 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648656)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ North and 166˚ to 176˚ West. Sheet no. 3 of 9. 7-10 October 1968.
    - 0674 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648656)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ North and 177˚ East to 176˚ West. Sheet no. 4 of 9. 11-15 October 1968.
    - 0675 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648656)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 0˚ to 6˚ North and 173˚ to 178˚ East. Sheet no. 5 of 9. 16-17 October 1968.
    - 0676 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648656)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 0˚ to 6˚ South and 178˚ West to 173˚ East. Sheet no. 6 of 9. 18-20 October 1968.
    - 0677 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648644)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 6˚ to 12˚ South and 168˚ to 179˚ West. Sheet no. 7 of 9. 21-23 October 1968.
    - 0678 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648644)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ South and 168˚ to 179˚ West. Sheet no. 8 of 9. 25-29 October 1968.
    - 0679 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Suva (Folder Barcode: 00275648644)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ South and 178˚ East to 178˚ West. Sheet no. 9 of 9. 30-31 October 1968.
    - 0680 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Brisbane (Folder Barcode: 00275648644)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 18˚ to 24˚ North and 158˚ to 161˚ West. Sheet no. 1 of 12. 28-29 March 1968.
    - 0681 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Brisbane (Folder Barcode: 00275648644)
      a. Ozalid paper. b. From 12˚ to 18˚ North and 160˚ to 166˚ West. Sheet no. 2 of 12. 30-31 March 1968.
    - 0682 Conrad Track, Honolulu to Brisbane (Folder Barcode: 00275648644)